Lazy Game Food Reviews
懒人游戏美食评测
I'm gonna start with some bacon.
今天咱先煎点培根
Just doing it on a stovetop over medium heat
开中火，把锅底烫热后放入
I really like doing it in the oven, actually for larger amounts more consistently.
实际上我更乐意将其放在烤箱里处理，这样它们出来的效果就一样了
But I want to in a pan today because I want that grease.
但是我更想用锅处理，因为我要其煎出的底油
Bacon!
好吃的培根！
Yeah.
:-D
All right. You know, lower the heat a little bit.
好的，你懂的，将锅底放凉一点
Get that grease go in there, and get some of these heirloom blue eggs.
底油就放在这里，然后我去拿点Heirloom（传家宝）牌蓝皮鸡蛋
So blue.
超蓝的呢
Pink himalayan sea salt.
先放点喜马拉雅粉盐
注：从喜马拉雅山脉600米的深矿中开采出来的盐，矿物质丰富
A little bit of onion powder.
一点洋葱粉
Some cracked peppercorn.
再磨点胡椒粉
And a bit of basil.
再放点罗勒（一种香叶）
And cover that for a bit to do its thing.
然后用锅盖焖上
Looking pretty good to me.
成型了，很好:-)
Bacon, eggs, and some berries.
培根啊，鸡蛋啊，还有一些莓类啥的
Few each of strawberries, raspberries, and blackberries. Yeah.
草莓，树莓和黑莓一样都来点。来点小资情调
Breakfast!
介就是早点啦！
Gotta get some coffee going.
再磨杯咖啡
And for that, I've got this fresh bag from South Slope Coffee here in Asheville, North Carolina.
我这回尝尝由北卡阿什维尔市South Slope Coffee厂产的新鲜咖啡豆
It's a Kenya something-or-other brand, and it's absolutely wonderful.
这上面写着Kenya（肯尼亚）啥的，而且是绝对好喝的
Has like this rich dark chocolaty kind of happiness smell to it.
豆子颜色很黑，跟巧克力一样。闻上去有种幸福的感觉
I don't know how to describe that.
不知道该怎么说了
Smells amazing already.
闻上去已经很香了
Now doing it as a pour-over, seems a disservice.
现在开始倒水，看上去放多了
Mostly because I just like making pour-overs.
也许我只是喜欢倒水吧:-|
Get the kettle going, I'll get it up there to around 205 degrees. Should very high in no time.
水倒完了，现在将水做到205华氏度，应该很快就能开
注：注意仪表盘下面，有摄氏度刻度
And that's that.
就是这样啦
And do it to get the container all warmed up,
然后这样来温杯和滤纸
and filter, get some water here it like using the reusable ones
在滤纸上倒水。一般我滤纸都得用好几遍
so I don't have to go through so much paper.
所以我没有必要费纸
That are all nice and warm, with the grounds.
杯具已温，现在来放鲜磨咖啡粉
I'm gonna make myself a couple cups here.
我大概要滤出个两大杯
So usually go like 20.5 ounces something like that.
所以大概应该是20.5盎司
Oh yeah! Smells great already.
好极了，闻上去很不错:-)
There we go.
好极了，就是这样
I don't know how well that's coming across on the scale,
我不知道在秤上要称出多少
but yeah, 20.8 ounces, 589 milliliters, 588 grams.
来看看，20.8盎司，589毫升，588克
Yeah, whatever anyway about there.
反正秤上是这么显示的
Gets me a couple of these. I love an ounce coffee mugs filled.
应该是两杯，我希望马克杯能给倒满
Now to wait.
现在再等等
And smell.
然后闻一下
Ah, it smell so good. I wish I could put smells through this videos, man.
啊，闻上去真醒脑。要是我能让各位隔屏闻香就好了
At least the good ones.
至少是这个不错的味道
Oh yeah, that is gonna go nicely with everything else.
好极了，这个和其他吃的放在一起真是绝配
Oh yeah, I don't always make a breakfast like this.
好吧，我不常这么做早点
But when I do, it has blackberries.
但是要是的话，我会来点黑莓
Mmm, I mean, you can do pickles in the morning, right?
反正，你大早晨会吃酸黄瓜的，对吧
I mean, you could, I have. But berries, mmm~
当然，没人会拦你。但是黑莓吗......:-)
Mmm Bacon.
再看看培根
Just enough chewing this. So juicy.
口感本身就很不错，十分多汁
Turns out it's tough to eat from a plate,
实际上，还是把盘子放在桌子上得劲
if you're just holding it trying to film and record yourself at the same time.
要是自寻苦吃，就边抬着碟子边吃吧:-\
But yeah - those eggs try to get him with just the right kind of crunch on the bottom,
但是呢......鸡蛋角下面煎的嘎儿真的是恰到好处
and that runs in the middle.
而且中间的也是很好
Yeah, I love making them this way. Bacon, grease.
是啊，这样做很好。拿煎培根搞出的油来煎鸡蛋
I don't know why I didn't start putting basil in my eggs until recently,
我只到最近才知道可以往鸡蛋上放香叶
but I did and now I just can't turn that.
但是这么一吃就欲罢不能了
And yeah, look at that.
再来欣赏欣赏
I don't know about you, but that's just how I like it.
不知道各位是啥看法，我十分喜欢这样
Just enough to get a little golden... I mean like eggs and pretty much any way.
底下煎得泛点金黄......反正像煎鸡蛋的就是这样啦
But for whatever reason, this particular recently is really done it for me.
无论如何，这样搞真的是很好
Get this lovely guy with the bacon, all intact.
这玩意就着培根，一口下去......
Oh~ holy crap. Oh man, so good-
LGR 陶醉中.
LGR 陶醉中..
LGR 陶醉中...
almost forgot about the coffee.
差点忘了这杯咖啡
And LGR mug, on sale now: lazygamereviews.com/shop.
光 速 吟 唱 中
注：该杯子售价11.99美元
Oh, I love this coffee.
啊，这咖啡真好喝
It's the first bunch I've had from south slope coffee in Asheville, but it's friggin great.
虽然是那个厂子产的头一批，但是尝起来确实不错啊
I've had it actually in some different shops.
我曾经在别的店里看见过
I hadn't made it myself until recently.
但是我直到最近才搞来一个
It's one of those that just... it's just so...
这个就是这么......怎么说呢......
You don't need anything else, at least I don't.
这什么都可以不加了，至少我是这么认为的
I've been trying to wean myself off the artificial sweeteners, and sugars, and all that.
我现在正在努力远离人造甜蜜素，还有糖之类的
And it's a really good coffee like this. You get that bit of,
这杯咖啡也是不错的，你能尝到那种
you know, red currant and dark chocolate, rosehip blackberry with actual berries.
额，红醋栗和黑巧克力，玫瑰果和黑莓。还有这些果子啥的
And just breakfasts with all kinds, sticks all these to my mouth.
早晨吃这堆果子，一口都吃掉
That's just perfect.
感觉真是美好
You got the berries chased with some of that coffee.
这些果子和咖啡一起在口腔里耳鬓厮磨:-)
All right, I'm gonna finish that coffee and this bacon.
好的，现在赶紧将这些咖啡和培根都消灭掉
And I hope you're hungry now, because I am... or at least I was.
最后呢，希望大家都馋了。因为我馋了......至少刚才是这样的
Mmm~ bacon...
本视频由SuperBart翻译，原作者LGR发布于2018-10-19